Somil **Athole**

Full Stack Developer & UX/UI Designer

Contact

Address

Bengaluru, India 560001

Phone

+917582093554

E-mail

sathole2001@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/somilathole-39915a15a

Websites, Portfolios, **Profiles**

• https://rad-jellye27695.netlify.app/

Technical Skills

DSA

C++

SQL

RestAPIs

Docker

Flutter

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React.Js

Node.Js

MongoDB

MySQL

Bootstrap

Sass

Webpack

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 1 years of related experience.

Professional Experience

Frontend Development Intern 2022-11 -2023-03

MirrAR Technologies, Noida

- Worked over 11 projects over the period.
- Worked on real-time projects to gain skills of frontend development.

2022-02 -**UX Design Intern**

CBNITS, Kolkata

- Worked with 6 clients over the period of 7 months and used experience to increase the user traffic by 50%.
- Worked on major project (Cortex XDR)'s introduction UI.

Education

2022-09

2023-10 Bachelor of Technology: Computer Science And **Engineering**

Vellore Institute of Technologies - Bhopal

- Member of VIT gaming Club.
- Student Ambassador of Internshala.

2019-03 Higher Secondary School: PCM

Raj Heights - The Global School - Bhopal, India

• Awarded as Top performer of the year in sports

2017-03 High School: PCM

JawaharLal Nehru School - Bhopal, India

• Completed professional development in PCM.

Projects

• Road Accidents Prediction Application using Machine Learning (capstone project)

Description: This application uses MI to sense accidents and send notification to the nearest hospital and top 3 contacts about the accident.

• Snake Game

Description: Used concepts of DSA.

Music Player

Description: This application is a simple music player with pre-loaded music.

Certifications

2023-01 Meta Front-end Developer Professional Certificate